# SIDIKA AVALIN **CHARSOOGHI**



# **PERSONAL INFO**

**Address** 

Östra Farmvägen 32C 21441 Malmö Sweden

Phone number 0722793412

**Email** 

scharsooghi@gmail.com

Linkedin

www.linkedin.com/in/sidika314

Github

https://github.com/scharsooghi/

#### TECHNICALSKILLS

HTML 5 CSS<sub>3</sub> **RWD Javascript** React JS 0000 Photoshop git scrum jira

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Persian (Native) **English** 

0000 Swedish

I am an enthusiastic, dedicated and hardworking person with a great passion for making userfriendly websites. Having the ability of high concentration and logical mind, I put my efforts into solving the problems efficiently. With 10 years of work experience and a master's degree in Computer Science, I have learned how to gradually improve the products step by step. I am a positive individual with strong interpersonal skills who believes to work as a team by considering co-workers' needs.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2020 - 2020 Frontend Web Developer | Intern Dec Sep

Yayloh, Stockholm - Sweden

Developing Yayloh return management platform as an intern front-end developer

2019 - Now Volunteer Job

Aug Crossroads, Skåne Stadsmission, Malmö - Sweden

I help homeless and jobless people and it's also helpful to improve my Swe dish.

2016 - 2018 Scratch and Math Teacher

Mar Sep Educational Complexes, Tehran - Iran

I taught scratch programming and math to elementary students.

2016 - 2016 **Frontend Web Developer** 

Mar Sep ACECR - Sharif University branch, Tehran - Iran

Developing ACECR business website.

2012 - 2016 **Technician in Information Security Management** 

May Mar ACECR - Sharif University branch, Tehran - Iran

> • ISMS and ITIL security consulting and auditioning for the data center of Iran National Organization for Civil Registration (NOCR)

• Knowledge managing in Connected Vehicle Technology (CVT) project

2010 - 2014 Web App Requirement Analysis, Designing and Testing

May Jul ACECR - Sharif University branch, Tehran - Iran

> • Designing, a nalyzing, testing and documenting NAMA Information Security Management System (ISMS) web application

• Testing and knowledge managing an Electronic Document Management System (EDMS) web application

2008 - 2008 Web Developer | Inern

National Organization of Educational Testing (NOET), Tehran - Iran

Developing a query engine web application using HTML, CSS, JS, Ajax and PHP as a bachelor's degree final project.

### **EDUCATION**

Jan

Sep

2010 - 2013 Master of Science Sep Feb Information Technology | University of Shahed - Tehran, Iran

2004 - 2008 **Bachelor of Science** Sep Sep Computer Science | Shahid Beheshti University – Tehran, Iran

## SOFT SKILLS

- Troubleshooting and Problem Solving
- Communication and Teamwork Skills
- Time Managing and Prioritizing Tasks
- Active Learning
- Organizational Commitment
- Concentration Skill

# HOBBIES













## COURSES

2020 – Now Fullstack Developeing

Nov Foocoding, Malmö - Sweden

Fullstack concepts such as HTML5, CSS3, RWD, JS, Reactjs, Nodejs, DB

2020 – 2020 Front-end Developing

Feb Aug Self-teaching via online courses

 $HTML5, CSS3, \,Responsive \,Web \,Design \,(RWD), Javascript, \,basic \,concepts \,in \,react js,$ 

such as components (Class and function), state and life style.

2009 – 2010 CIW

Mar Dec Academic Center for Education, Culture and Research in SBU

During the Web Design Specialist (CIW) course I learned how to design and publish

Web sites.

### ACHIEVEMENTS

- Teacher of the Month | Meshkaat Educational Complex School in March 2017
- Third laureate for "Design and Implementation of Connected Vehicle System" | 28<sup>th</sup> Khwarizmi International Award, 2015.
- Employee of the year | ACECR IT Department in 2014

#### REFERENCES

References are available upon request.